hillsdale.edu 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy - Hillsdale College

Welcome visitors!  This Privacy Policy explains the information collected by Hillsdale College from visitor activity at [hillsdale.edu](https://www.hillsdale.edu/) (the “Site”) and how we use it.

#### How you accept this Policy

By visiting the Site or by otherwise providing us with personally identifiable information.

#### Information we collect that is not personally-identifiable

We collect information that is not personally identifiable (meaning, anonymous information) regarding use of the Site, such as login information, computer-related information (browser type you used, your Internet Protocol address, last URL visited, and the date and time of day of your login).  We send a “cookie” or “pixel tag” to your computer which contains an identification number that is unique to the computer you are using.  You may decline to provide such information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result, and some services may not be available.

We use this anonymous information to enhance the visitor experience at the Site, to understand how our Site is used, to communicate with our visitors about information and services relating to the Site, to investigate and verify proper conduct at the Site, and to monitor the security and integrity of the Site.  Internally, we use data in the aggregate to analyze our business.

#### What we collect about you that is personally identifiable (“PI”) and how we use it

We do not collect information that is personally identifiable unless you provide it to us (such as your name and email address) so that you can receive further communications from us, including advertising and promotion. You can opt out of receiving future emails and electronic communications.  We may disclose PI as required by law and/or in response to service of legal process, such as a court order, summons, subpoena, and the like.  We use PI to investigate and verify proper conduct at the Site, and to monitor the security and integrity of the Site.  We do not share or sell your PI with or to third parties.

#### Agent

An “Agent” is any third party that collects or uses personal information under the instructions of, and solely for, Hillsdale College, or a third party to which Hillsdale College discloses personal information for use on Hillsdale College ‘s behalf.  Agents shall comply with the privacy obligations stated in this Policy.

How you can access or change the PI that we have collected:  If you have provided PI to us and wish to revoke our use of it, you will need to email us a written request to cease use of your name and email address.

#### Information About Children

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

#### Links to other websites

We may provide links to third party websites.  We are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those sites, including their privacy policies.  Please review the privacy policies of such sites.

#### Changes to this policy

If we make any significant changes to this policy, we will notify you by email, or post a notice of such changes on the Sites, or flag our Privacy Policy on the Sites as updated.

#### Effective date

This Privacy Policy is effective June 1, 2014.

#### Contact

Please contact us with any questions and/or comments you may have.

Hillsdale College  
33 East College Street  
Hillsdale, Michigan 49242  
Telephone: (517) 437-7341
